petssa.co.za 2018-12-25

# PRIVACY POLICY

PRIVACY POLICY

**PetsSA Commitment to Privacy**

Petssa.co.za is committed to protecting the privacy of those using our Site and the confidentiality of the personal information with which our users provide us on the Site. This privacy policy explains the steps we take to ensure information about you is kept secure and confidential.

Please read this privacy policy carefully, as once you use our website or our services you will be deemed to have read and accepted this privacy policy.

Your personal information is safe with us. Links to third party sites appear on the Site. Those third party sites are not our responsibility, although we choose them with care. You should read and satisfy yourself with those third parties' privacy policies before using such linked sites. We will always let you have a copy of all personal information we have about you should you request it. You are able to update and amend your personal information at any time by visiting [www.petssa.co.za](http://www.petssa.co.za/). You can also unsubscribe from [www.petssa.co.za](http://www.petssa.co.za/) at any time by following the unsubscribe link in our email communications.

**Purposes for which we use information about our users**

We collect information about our users for a variety of purposes. These include: •where you supply information to us in order that we deliver a required service e.g. newsletters relevant to you and your interests, information will be processed by us to supply the information and material which we promise. Your information is held at petssa.co.za in South Africa, and maintained by Petssa.co.za and yourself via [www.petssa.co.za](http://www.petssa.co.za/). •so we can communicate with you in response to a specific action performed by you on this site e.g. when you add a directory listing, leave a review, enter a competition, place an ad. •so we can inform you of new competitions, special events and services which may be of interest •to help us improve and personalise our services

**Passing on information about you**

We will not pass on any information provided by you to any third parties unless you specifically consent. We may however disclose aggregate – but not individual – statistics to potential partners and advertisers, such as the number of users we have, their location, etc. If you give your consent, third parties may then occasionally send communications to you to provide information, offers and services that may be of interest to you. Please note that within the MultimediaSA Group, Pets SA may from time to time send communications, promotional data to you to provide information, offers and services that may be of interest to all our users. This is within the use of our site and all users using our site consent to this term. 

**Security**

Keeping information about you secure is very important to us. However, no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be totally secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information which you send to us, and you do so at your own risk.

Petssa.co.za will take precautions to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your user data under our control. Only authorised employees and subcontractors will be given access to the information you provide us. Our systems are designed to ensure that your data can only be viewed online if your email and password are correctly input. While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration to data will not occur, we take many precautions aimed at preventing such occurrences.

You are ultimately responsible for the security of your email and password. Please take care when using and storing them. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. You should log out of your browser at the end of each computer session to ensure that others cannot access your personal information, especially if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or internet café.

**Cookies**

[www.petssa.co.za](http://www.petssa.co.za/) makes use of cookies to personalise content and provide statistics that allow us to understand how users use the website, helping us to improve its structure and content. Although some website operators use cookies to generate consumer profiling information to be sold or transferred to third parties, it is the policy of this site never to share information collected using cookies with third parties.

**Disabling / enabling cookies**

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser. However, you may not be able to use all the interactive features of our sites if cookies are disabled. To find out how to disable / enable cookies or for more general information about cookies got to [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

Yours sincerely

Pets SA Team
